Felipe Braga

Minas Gerais, Brazil



mr.felipebraga@gmail.com



38999502626



linkedin.com/in/mrfelipebraga

Summary

I'm a Full Stack developer, with about 4 years working in web development. I have a degree in Computer Science. I have worked in the implementation of new projects and maintenance of legacy projects. I have knowledge in DevOps, Javascript, Node.js, NextJS, Nest.js, Solid, Git, relational and non-relational databases, tests and scrum ceremonies (journal, sprint review, among others).

Experience



Full Stack Developer

R-Dias Especialistas em Varejo

Sep 2021 - Present (1 year 6 months)



Full Stack Developer

Cardio Web

Feb 2020 - Sep 2021 (1 year 8 months)

Development of new projects and maintenance of legacy projects.

Main projects:

- 1. Electrocardiogram reception system with generation of reports and reports.
- 2. Mobile application with Bluetooth connection to the electrocardiogram device to check cables and battery level.

Technologies used: React Native, React.js, hapi.js, Redis, RabbitMQ, AngularJS, GitLab and MongoDB.



Full Stack Developer

Cardio Web

Feb 2019 - Feb 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Legacy system maintenance and implementation of new features.



Web Designer

Agência 99 Cores

Mar 2017 - Dec 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Development of institutional websites, virtual stores, blogs, landing pages and hotsites.

Main projects:

- 1. Creation of an ERP for a massage therapy company to manage spa employees.
- 2. Creation and maintenance of virtual stores in OpenCart sharing the database between stores with a parent store.

Technologies used: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, PHP, AngularJS, WordPress, OpenCart, Tray and MySQL.

Education



Universidade UNG

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2016 - 2019



IFNMG - Campus Salinas

Technical, Computing 2013 - 2015

Skills

JavaScript • Next.js • Node.js • Git • React Native • React.js • MongoDB • hapi.js • nodejs • AngularJS